Tuftonian UP001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tuftonian, 1874 -- 1965; UP001.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 60 Volumes
  - Tuftonian, October 5, 1887; UP001.001.006.00001 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, October 20, 1887; UP001.001.006.00002 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1887; UP001.001.006.00003 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, November 21, 1887; UP001.001.006.00004 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1887; UP001.001.006.00005 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1887; UP001.001.006.00006 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, January 20, 1888; UP001.001.006.00007 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, February 5, 1888; UP001.001.006.00008 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1888; UP001.001.006.00009 (Box Volume 6)
  - Tuftonian, March 5, 1888; UP001.001.006.00010 (Box Volume 6)
  - Tuftonian, March 20, 1888; UP001.001.006.00011 (Box Volume 6)
  - Tuftonian, April 5, 1888; UP001.001.006.00012 (Box Volume 6)
  - Tuftonian, April 20, 1888; UP001.001.006.00013 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, May 5, 1888; UP001.001.006.00014 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1888; UP001.001.006.00015 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, June 5, 1888; UP001.001.006.00016 (Box Volume 6, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, June 20, 1888; UP001.001.006.00017 (Box Volume 6)
    Rev. J Coleman Adams, Strongly Urges Co-education at Commencement, 1888; Alumni day
  - Tuftonian, October 5, 1888; UP001.001.007.00001 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room.
  - Tuftonian, October 20, 1888; UP001.001.007.00002 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1888; UP001.001.007.00003 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, November 20, 1888; UP001.001.007.00004 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1888; UP001.001.007.00005 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1888; UP001.001.007.00006 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_7563475e916c1ce6dfbeb77dcdc70e8c)
  - Tuftonian, January 19, 1889; UP001.001.007.00007 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, February 5, 1889; UP001.001.007.00008 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1889; UP001.001.007.00009 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, March 5, 1889; UP001.001.007.00010 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, March 20, 1889; UP001.001.007.00011 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, April 5, 1889; UP001.001.007.00012 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, April 20, 1889; UP001.001.007.00013 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, May 4, 1889; UP001.001.007.00014 (Box Volume 7)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1889; UP001.001.007.00015 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, June 5, 1889; UP001.001.007.00016 (Box Volume 7)
  - Tuftonian, June 20, 1889; UP001.001.007.00017 (Box Volume 7, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni day [includes poem by Rev. E.A. Start
  - Tuftonian, October 5, 1889; UP001.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, October 21, 1889; UP001.001.008.00002 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1889; UP001.001.008.00003 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, November 20, 1889; UP001.001.008.00004 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1889; UP001.001.008.00005 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1889; UP001.001.008.00006 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, January 20, 1890; UP001.001.008.00007 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, February 5, 1890; UP001.001.008.00008 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1890; UP001.001.008.00009 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, March 5, 1890; UP001.001.008.00010 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tuftonian, March 20, 1890; UP001.001.008.00011 (Box Volume 8)
  - Tuftonian, April 5, 1890; UP001.001.008.00012 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, April 21, 1890; UP001.001.008.00013 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, May 5, 1890; UP001.001.008.00014 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1890; UP001.001.008.00015 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, June 5, 1890; UP001.001.008.00016 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, June 20, 1890; UP001.001.008.00017 (Box Volume 8, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, October 6, 1890; UP001.001.009.00001 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, October 20, 1890; UP001.001.009.00002 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1890; UP001.001.009.00003 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, November 20, 1890; UP001.001.009.00004 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1890; UP001.001.009.00005 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1890; UP001.001.009.00006 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_c13559f28bea3eac0f484610e23833da)
  - Tuftonian, January 20, 1891; UP001.001.009.00007 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, February 5, 1891; UP001.001.009.00008 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1891; UP001.001.009.00009 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, March 5, 1891; UP001.001.009.00010 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, March 20, 1891; UP001.001.009.00011 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, April 6, 1891; UP001.001.009.00012 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, April 20, 1891; UP001.001.009.00013 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, May 5, 1891; UP001.001.009.00014 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1891; UP001.001.009.00015 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, June 5, 1891; UP001.001.009.00016 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, June 20, 1891; UP001.001.009.00017 (Box Volume 9, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, October 5, 1891; UP001.001.010.00001 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, October 20, 1891; UP001.001.010.00002 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1891; UP001.001.010.00003 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, November 20, 1891; UP001.001.010.00004 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1891; UP001.001.010.00005 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1891; UP001.001.010.00006 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, January 20, 1892; UP001.001.010.00007 (Box Volume 10)
  - Tuftonian, February 5, 1892; UP001.001.010.00008 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1892; UP001.001.010.00009 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, March 5, 1892; UP001.001.010.00010 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, March 21, 1892; UP001.001.010.00011 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, April 5, 1892; UP001.001.010.00012 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, April 20, 1892; UP001.001.010.00013 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, May 5, 1892; UP001.001.010.00014 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1892; UP001.001.010.00015 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, June 6, 1892; UP001.001.010.00016 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, June 25, 1892; UP001.001.010.00017 (Box Volume 10, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, October 5, 1892; UP001.001.011.00001 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, October 20, 1892; UP001.001.011.00002 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1892; UP001.001.011.00003 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, November 20, 1892; UP001.001.011.00004 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1892; UP001.001.011.00005 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1892; UP001.001.011.00006 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, January 20, 1893; UP001.001.011.00007 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, February 4, 1893; UP001.001.011.00008 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1893; UP001.001.011.00009 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, March 6, 1893; UP001.001.011.00010 (Box Volume 11)
  - Tuftonian, March 20, 1893; UP001.001.011.00011 (Box Volume 11)
  - Tuftonian, April 5, 1893; UP001.001.011.00012 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, April 20, 1893; UP001.001.011.00013 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, May 5, 1893; UP001.001.011.00014 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1893; UP001.001.011.00015 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, June 5, 1893; UP001.001.011.00016 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, June 26, 1893; UP001.001.011.00017 (Box Volume 11, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, October 20, 1893; UP001.001.012.00001 (Box Volume 12, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1893; UP001.001.012.00002 (Box Volume 12, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, November 20, 1893; UP001.001.012.00003 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1893; UP001.001.012.00004 (Box Volume 12, Box data_value_missing_a448c803022712df1f22902100c48cfc)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1893; UP001.001.012.00005 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, January 20, 1894; UP001.001.012.00006 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, February 5, 1894; UP001.001.012.00007 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1894; UP001.001.012.00008 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, March 5, 1894; UP001.001.012.00009 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, March 20, 1894; UP001.001.012.00010 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, April 5, 1894; UP001.001.012.00011 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, April 20, 1894; UP001.001.012.00012 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, May 5, 1894; UP001.001.012.00013 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1894; UP001.001.012.00014 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, June 5, 1894; UP001.001.012.00015 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, Commencement Numeber, 1894; UP001.001.012.00016 (Box Volume 12)
  - Tuftonian, October 5, 1894; UP001.001.013.00001 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, October 20, 1894; UP001.001.013.00002 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, November 5, 1894; UP001.001.013.00003 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, November 20, 1894; UP001.001.013.00004 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, December 5, 1894; UP001.001.013.00005 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, December 20, 1894; UP001.001.013.00006 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, January 20, 1895; UP001.001.013.00007 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, February 5, 1895; UP001.001.013.00008 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, February 20, 1895; UP001.001.013.00009 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, March 5, 1895; UP001.001.013.00010 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, March 20, 1895; UP001.001.013.00011 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, April 20, 1895; UP001.001.013.00012 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, May 6, 1895; UP001.001.013.00013 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, May 20, 1895; UP001.001.013.00014 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, June 5, 1895; UP001.001.013.00015 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, June 20, 1895; UP001.001.013.00016 (Box Volume 13)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1895; UP001.001.014.00001 (Box Volume 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. The Tufts News Vol. I, no. 1-Vol. I, no. 4 April-May, 1912 The Tufts News Vol. I, no. 1-Vol. I, no. 4 April-May, 1912
  - Tuftonian, December, 1895; UP001.001.014.00002 (Box Volume 14)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1896; UP001.001.014.00003 (Box Volume 14)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1896; UP001.001.014.00004 (Box Volume 14)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1896; UP001.001.014.00005 (Box Volume 14)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1896; UP001.001.014.00006 (Box Volume 14)
  - Tuftonian, May-June, 1896; UP001.001.014.00007 (Box Volume 14)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1896; UP001.001.015.00001 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1896; UP001.001.015.00002 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1896; UP001.001.015.00003 (Box Volume 15)
    John Coleman Adams. The Americanism of James Russell Lowell.
  - Tuftonian, January, 1897; UP001.001.015.00004 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1897; UP001.001.015.00005 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1897; UP001.001.015.00006 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1897; UP001.001.015.00007 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tuftonian, May-June, 1897; UP001.001.015.00008 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1898; UP001.001.016.00001 (Box Volume 16)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1899; UP001.001.016.00002 (Box Volume 16)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1899; UP001.001.016.00003 (Box Volume 16)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1899; UP001.001.016.00004 (Box Volume 16)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1899; UP001.001.016.00005 (Box Volume 16)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1899; UP001.001.017.00001 (Box Volume 17)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1899; UP001.001.017.00002 (Box Volume 17)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1899; UP001.001.017.00003 (Box Volume 17)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1900; UP001.001.017.00004 (Box Volume 17)
    John Coleman Adams. A Dramatic Moment.
  - Tuftonian, February, 1900; UP001.001.017.00005 (Box Volume 17)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1900; UP001.001.017.00006 (Box Volume 17)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1900; UP001.001.018.00001 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1900; UP001.001.018.00002 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1900; UP001.001.018.00003 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1901; UP001.001.018.00004 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1901; UP001.001.018.00005 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1901; UP001.001.018.00006 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1901; UP001.001.018.00007 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1901; UP001.001.018.00008 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1901; UP001.001.018.00009 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1901; UP001.001.019.00001 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1901; UP001.001.019.00002 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1901; UP001.001.019.00003 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1902; UP001.001.019.00004 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1902; UP001.001.019.00005 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1902; UP001.001.019.00006 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1902; UP001.001.019.00007 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1902; UP001.001.019.00008 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1902; UP001.001.019.00009 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1902; UP001.001.020.00001 (Box Volume 20)
    [Alumni and Faculty, Famous] Marvin, Winthrop Lippitt (1884) A Tufts assistant secretary of the Navy (Charles Hial Darling), p. 3-9.
  - Tuftonian, November, 1902; UP001.001.020.00002 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1902; UP001.001.020.00003 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1903; UP001.001.020.00004 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1903; UP001.001.020.00005 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1903; UP001.001.020.00006 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1903; UP001.001.020.00007 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1903; UP001.001.020.00008 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1903; UP001.001.020.00009 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1903; UP001.001.021.00001 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1903; UP001.001.021.00002 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1903; UP001.001.021.00003 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1904; UP001.001.021.00004 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1904; UP001.001.021.00005 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1904; UP001.001.021.00006 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1904; UP001.001.021.00007 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1904; UP001.001.021.00008 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1904; UP001.001.022.00001 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1904; UP001.001.022.00002 (Box Volume 22)
    Katherine Adams. A Child's Fear of the Dark.
  - Tuftonian, December, 1904; UP001.001.022.00003 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1905; UP001.001.022.00004 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1905; UP001.001.022.00005 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1905; UP001.001.022.00006 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1905; UP001.001.022.00007 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1905; UP001.001.022.00008 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1905; UP001.001.022.00009 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1905; UP001.001.023.00001 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1905; UP001.001.023.00002 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1905; UP001.001.023.00003 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1906; UP001.001.023.00004 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1906; UP001.001.023.00005 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1906; UP001.001.023.00006 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1906; UP001.001.023.00007 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1906; UP001.001.023.00008 (Box Volume 23)
    [Admann, A. B.] After Exams. pp. 242-243
  - Tuftonian, June, 1906; UP001.001.023.00009 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1906; UP001.001.024.00001 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1906; UP001.001.024.00002 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1906; UP001.001.024.00003 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1907; UP001.001.024.00004 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1907; UP001.001.024.00005 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1907; UP001.001.024.00006 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1907; UP001.001.024.00007 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1907; UP001.001.024.00008 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1907; UP001.001.024.00009 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1907; UP001.001.025.00001 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1907; UP001.001.025.00002 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1907; UP001.001.025.00003 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1908; UP001.001.025.00004 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1908; UP001.001.025.00005 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1908; UP001.001.025.00006 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1908; UP001.001.025.00007 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1908; UP001.001.025.00008 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1908; UP001.001.025.00009 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1908; UP001.001.026.00001 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1908; UP001.001.026.00002 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1909; UP001.001.026.00003 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1909; UP001.001.026.00004 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1909; UP001.001.026.00005 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1909; UP001.001.026.00006 (Box Volume 26)
    Gladys Marion Adams. The Call of the Wind.
  - Tuftonian, May, 1909; UP001.001.026.00007 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1909; UP001.001.026.00008 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, July, 1909; UP001.001.026.00009 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tuftonian, October, 1909; UP001.001.027.00001 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1909; UP001.001.027.00002 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1909; UP001.001.027.00003 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1910; UP001.001.027.00004 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1910; UP001.001.027.00005 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1910; UP001.001.027.00006 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1910; UP001.001.027.00007 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1910; UP001.001.027.00008 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, July, 1910; UP001.001.027.00009 (Box Volume 27)
    Gladys Marion Adams. The Myth: Its Interpretations in the Light of Modern Science.
  - Tuftonian, October, 1910; UP001.001.027.00010 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, November, 1910; UP001.001.027.00011 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, December, 1910; UP001.001.027.00012 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, January, 1911; UP001.001.027.00013 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, February, 1911; UP001.001.027.00014 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, March, 1911; UP001.001.027.00015 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, April, 1911; UP001.001.027.00016 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1911; UP001.001.027.00017 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, June, 1911; UP001.001.027.00018 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tuftonian, May, 1926; UP001.001.028.00001 (Box Volume 28)
  - Tuftonian, August, 1926; UP001.001.028.00002 (Box Volume 28)
    [Alumni day] The Tower cross (poem) read at banquet by Charles H. Stone [A1906]; Jane Addams (H 1926). Honorary Degree recipient (photos with Miss Louise Bowen); Alumni association meetings
  - Tuftonian, January, 1927; UP001.001.028.00003 (Box Volume 28)
  - Tuftonian, index, January 1927-August 1928, 1927 -- 1928; UP001.001.030.00001 (Box 30)
  - Tuftonian, August, 1927; UP001.001.028.00004 (Box Volume 28)
    Herbert Adams. Honorary Degree Recipient, 1927; Alumni association meetings; Alumni day; Alumni trustees